The eye will receive these light photons at the retina.
眼睛将在视网膜处接收这些光子。
The light rays first pass through all the layers,
光线首先穿过所有层，
to reach a place called photoreceptors.
到达一个我们称之为感光器的位置。
These photoreceptors are active because they are also in an area
这些感光器是活跃的，因为它们也位于一个区域，
called the pigmented area.
我们称之为色素区。
A pigmented area, first layer here.
一个色素区，这是第一层。
Then you have what are called photoreceptors.
然后是所谓的感光器。
which are of two types, called cones and rods,
它们有两种，我们称之为视锥细胞和视杆细胞。
then it will
然后它会
pass through a layer of cells called bipolar cells
穿过一层细胞，我们称之为双极细胞。
then it will go to another layer of cells called ganglion cells
然后它会到达另一层细胞，我们称之为
and it is they who will gather all their axons will gather
神经节细胞，它们将汇集所有轴突，
to gather
汇集
to form the optic nerve and
形成视神经，并
therefore transform the trans
因此进行转换。
Reproduction happens at this level.
繁殖发生在这个层面。
Now, if we go a little further, we see photoreceptors.
现在，如果我们再深入一点，我们会看到感光器。
We see this layer of bipolar cells and ganglion cells.
我们看到双极细胞和神经节细胞的这一层。
And we see another new layer of cells called horizontal cells.
我们还看到一层新的细胞，我们称之为水平细胞。
We saw them a little bit here.
我们在这里看到了一点。
Horizontal cells that allow to capture information
水平细胞可以捕获信息
and redistribute it to the bipolar cells first.
并将其重新分配给首先是双极细胞。
Then below, you still have...
然后下面，你还有...
Another layer, before the ganglion cells, called amacrine cells.
在神经节细胞之前，还有另一层，我们称之为无长突细胞。
Again, so as not to lose all the information that would arrive,
同样，为了不丢失所有可能到达的信息，
it will again gather these cells and redirect them.
它会再次聚集这些细胞并重新定向。
So that gives us quite a lot of information already to capture.
所以这已经为我们提供了不少信息来捕获。
Let's take the example of a photoreceptor here that has the shape of a cone.
我们以一个锥形感光器为例。
And we see that this photoreceptor is made of an outer segment, an
我们看到这个感光器由一个外节、一个
inner segment.
内节组成。
a nucleus and a synaptic terminal.
一个细胞核和一个突触末梢。
In the outer segment, you have what are called plasma membranes
在外节中，有我们称之为
membranes
质膜的结构。
and you have an assembly of small discs.
并且有一组小盘。
And in these small discs, you have what is called a protein,
在这些小盘中，有一种我们称之为蛋白质的物质，
called opsin.
我们称之为视蛋白。
For the rod, this opsin is called rhodopsin
对于视杆细胞，这种视蛋白被称为视紫红质，
and for the cones.
对于视锥细胞。
Iodopsin.
碘视紫红质。
Now, you imagine, we are at the level of these photoreceptors.
现在，想象一下，我们正处于这些感光器的水平。
We see that at the level of the rods,
我们看到在视杆细胞中，
there is a small molecule attached to this rhodopsin
有一个小分子附着在视紫红质上，
called retinal.
叫做视黄醛。
You have these small stacked discs.
您有这些堆叠的小盘。
We go inside these small discs.
我们进入这些小盘的内部。
We have rhodopsin, it's a protein,
我们有视紫红质，它是一种蛋白质，
to which a molecule called retinal is attached.
上面附着着一个我们称之为视黄醛的分子。
The moment the light hits, it was like this, and it will change shape.
当光线照射时，它原来是这样，然后它会改变
shape.
形状。
It will make a movement like this.
它会像这样移动。
This retinal changes shape and transforms rhodopsin into
这个视黄醛改变形状，将视紫红质转化为
metarhodopsin.
变视紫红质。
And this transformation triggers a succession of chemical cascades at the cellular membrane level.
这种转化在细胞膜层面引发了一系列
chemical cascades
化学级联反应，
which will prevent sodium from entering.
阻止钠离子进入。
Non-permeability of the membrane.
膜的非渗透性。
and this non-permeability of the membrane creates, as we have already seen,
而这种膜的非渗透性，正如我们已经看到的，
simply an ionic change, among others to sodium ions,
仅仅是离子变化，主要是钠离子，
and it creates a membrane potential that creates a nerve impulse, which
它产生了一个膜电位，从而产生了一个神经冲动，它
changes.
改变了。
So it's simply an ionic change of the membrane
所以这仅仅是膜的离子变化，
which becomes permeable and non-permeable,
它变得可渗透和不可渗透，
and so the impulse changes and creates, as we had already seen, simply
因此，冲动改变并产生，正如我们已经看到的，仅仅是
an impulse.
一个冲动。
So the light arrives, it passes through all the layers.
所以光线到达，它穿过所有层。
I must have what is called a pigment here.
我必须有这里所说的色素。
And this pigment, where do we find it?
这种色素在哪里找到？
We find ourselves in beta-carotene, in carrots.
我们在β-胡萝卜素中找到它，在胡萝卜中。
It's vitamin A.
它是维生素A。
Important to activate in this opsin, in
对于激活这种视蛋白，在
this rhodopsin or in these iodopsins,
这种视紫红质或这些视锥蛋白中，
it will activate phenomena.
它将激活一些现象。
You have photoreceptors, the cones.
您有感光细胞，即视锥细胞。
Cones or rods will mainly be found in the peripheral retina.
视锥细胞或视杆细胞主要存在于视网膜周边。
This somewhat peripheral vision, there, is a vision that is not very detailed,
这种有点周边的视觉，细节很少，
which is, however, sensitive to light and has no color.
但它对光敏感，没有颜色。
While cone cells, they give a lot of detail,
而视锥细胞则提供很多细节，
they are not very sensitive and it gives color and central vision.
它们不那么敏感，但能提供颜色和中央视觉。
Cone cells, you have cone cells,
视锥细胞，您有视锥细胞，
For blue, red and green, these are shadow lengths that make
对于蓝色、红色和绿色，它们是波长，它们产生
arrive and these are types of opsins that will be found.
到达，这些是视蛋白的类型。
Now, I'll take it again. The rods. Three parts. Outer segment, inner segment,
现在，我再说一遍。视杆细胞。三部分。外节、内节、
inner segment, synaptic terminal.
突触末梢。
What interests us is the outer segment. The outer segment contains a lot of
我们感兴趣的是外节。外节包含许多
small discs.
小盘。
These small discs are called opsin.
这些小盘被称为视蛋白。
These opsins are called, in the case of rods, rhodopsin,
在视杆细胞中，这些视蛋白被称为视紫红质，
and in the case of cones, iodopsin.
在视锥细胞中，被称为视蓝质。
Opsin, the name we will find for rods or for cones.
视蛋白，是视杆细胞或视锥细胞中会发现的名称。
If now we go further, we see that, for example, at the level of the rods, rhodopsin, so
如果我们现在深入探讨，我们会发现，例如，在视杆细胞中，视紫红质，也就是
opsin, becomes rhodopsin.
视蛋白，变成了视紫红质。
In this rhodopsin, you have molecules.
在这种视紫红质中，有分子。
And these molecules are called retinal, which in fact changes its
这些分子被称为视黄醛，它实际上改变了
shape and makes this rhodopsin become meta-rhodopsin.
形状，使这种视紫红质变成了变视紫红质。
Changes shape.
改变形状。
And the change in shape creates a chemical cascade at the
形状的改变在
membrane level which causes the polarity of the membrane to change and
膜层面引起化学级联反应，导致膜的极性改变并
becomes impermeable.
变得不透水。
I can't get in anymore, right?
我不能再进去了，对吗？
I'm a sodium ion, you see, it's over, bang, for
我是一个钠离子，你看，结束了，啪，在
a given moment.
某个时刻。
And then after, I can, and it makes a membrane change
然后，我可以，这导致了膜的改变，
that creates the electric current.
从而产生了电流。
And it's always like that.
一直都是这样。
And so, it's just a molecular cascade, and it's even more, it's an ionic cascade
所以，这只是一个分子级联反应，甚至更多，这是一个
of sodium ions, you see.
钠离子级联反应，你看。
I can, I can't anymore.
我可以，我不能再。
I can, I can't anymore, I can, I can't anymore.
我可以，我不能再，我可以，我不能再。
I can, I can't anymore, so...
我可以，我不能再，所以……
I'm moving forward.
我继续。
And that creates the impulse.
它产生了神经冲动。
That's how I get this transduction.
这就是我进行这种转导的方式。
Do you understand?
你明白吗？
The transmission of light energy takes place in the photoreceptors.
光能的传递发生在光感受器中。
So it starts with the absorption of what?
那么，它从什么开始吸收呢？
Of photons.
光子。
It will create the variation of the photoreceptor membrane.
这将导致光感受器膜的变化。
By a sensitive pigment, opsin.
通过一种敏感的色素，视蛋白。
It is called rhodopsin or iodopsin, depending on whether we are on cones
根据是在视锥细胞
or rods.
还是视杆细胞上，我们称之为视紫红质或视蓝质。
And so, they are located on small discs in
因此，它们位于小盘状结构中，
the outer segment of the rod.
在视杆细胞的外节部分。
Now, we go in with the microscope.
现在，我们用显微镜观察。
We go into these small discs.
我们进入这些小盘状结构。
When the light arrives and touches, it changes shape, which
当光线到达并触及它时，它会改变形状，这
which causes a chemical cascade.
会引起一系列的化学反应。
It is linked to rhodopsin, because there is a conformational change of
这与视紫红质有关，因为一种叫做视黄醛的分子发生了构象变化，
a molecule called retinal, which will
它将
trigger this transduction phenomenon because it will change the shape of the retinal, which
触发这种转导现象，因为它会改变视黄醛的形状，视黄醛
absorbs light and allows rhodopsin to turn into metarhodopsin, which makes
吸收光线，使视紫红质转化为变视紫红质，从而使
the membrane, this plasma membrane here.
细胞膜，即这里的质膜。
Less permeable to sodium, we can no longer enter, which in fact creates a change
对钠的通透性降低，钠离子无法再进入，这实际上造成了通透性的变化，
in permeability, which will modify the membrane potential
这将改变膜电位，
and which will allow the emission of a nerve impulse to the next cell.
并允许神经冲动传递到下一个细胞。
And it's the same pattern. And that's where we have the importance of vitamin
这是相同的模式。这就是维生素A的重要性所在，
A, because it is necessary for the synthesis of retinal
因为它是视黄醛合成所必需的。
of this molecule to manufacture...
这种分子用于制造...
This molecule, I need vitamin A and if I have a vitamin A deficiency,
这种分子，我需要维生素A，如果我缺乏维生素
A, I will actually have a loss of sight, especially
A，我实际上会视力下降，尤其是在
at night.
夜间。